Pressure Point is a thriller, action film directed by Eric Weston.
While on vacation, Jed Griffin and his family cross paths with Rudy Wicker, a
cold-blooded killer who has just held up a bank and killed a sheriff's wife.
Rudy commandeers the Griffins' motor home, shoots Jed and assumes his identity
Jed Griffin, played by Michael Madsen.
Haley Griffin, played by Victoria Snow.
Shane Griffin, played by Ricky Mabe.
Tiffany Griffin, played by Samantha E. Cutler.
Rudy Wicker, played by Jeff Wincott.
Tracy Hunt, played by Claudia Besso.
Pressure Point, titled Pris au piège in French, is a 2001 Canadian
suspense thriller film starring Michael Madsen and Jeff Wincott.
Directed by Eric Weston, the film was distributed direct-to-video and was the first
release for Velocity Home Entertainment, a subsidiary of ThinkFilm.
The film also features Ricky Mabe.
The tone is intense.